<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on GeekLaunch</title>
    <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on GeekLaunch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jacob Lindahl</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://geeklaunch.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to switch GitHub Pages to a new domain for free using Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/how-to-switch-github-pages-to-a-new-domain-for-free-using-cloudflare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/how-to-switch-github-pages-to-a-new-domain-for-free-using-cloudflare/</guid>
      <description>For reasons consisting of little more than vanity, I decided to puchase the domain geeklaunch.io and port this website over to it, replacing geeklaunch.net. However, I wanted to make sure that I maintained as much of my measly SEO rankings as possible, as well as not break any of the links to geeklaunch.net that may exist around the web.
Setting the DNS records on the new domain For GitHub Pages, which is the hosting service I currently use for this website, the process for setting up a new domain to point at GitHub Pages is pretty well-documented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ウィスコンシン州の北地方</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/%E3%82%A6%E3%82%A3%E3%82%B9%E3%82%B3%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B7%E3%83%B3%E5%B7%9E%E3%81%AE%E5%8C%97%E5%9C%B0%E6%96%B9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/%E3%82%A6%E3%82%A3%E3%82%B9%E3%82%B3%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B7%E3%83%B3%E5%B7%9E%E3%81%AE%E5%8C%97%E5%9C%B0%E6%96%B9/</guid>
      <description>淡水湖の世界最大を思い描いてほしい。どういう感じだろう？賑やかな魚か、カヤックしている家族たちか？または、もしかしたら汚くて藻でいっぱいの湖なのか？
スペリオル湖は表面積で世界最大の淡水湖だ。狼の頭の形をし、北米土人語で「ギッチグミ」1と言う。
北ウィスコンシン州で「スペリオル湖と言って、一つ目に出てくる考えは何？」と聞いたら、統一的な返事は出てこないだろう。しかし、さまざまな意見の中から、みんなが賛成することは「スペリオル湖は冷たい」であることは間違いない。NASA によると、今年の７月に、水面温度は９度を超えなかった。
でも、冷たい水を怖がる必要はない。逆に、経験を楽しくすることができる。温度が低いおかげで、キモい藻が生えないし、飲めるほど綺麗だし、遠慮なく楽しめる。個人的に言えば、泳ぐのも好きだ！
スペリオル湖の岸には多くの自然公園があり、キャンプやハイキングができる場所が多い。最も田舎にある地方として、このような自然に囲まれていることが独自の文化を培っている。農場主や牧場主、猟師、漁師が一緒に暮らし、お互いに助け合ううちに、非常に実生活に基づいた世界観を持つようになった。
北ウィスコンシン州では農業がもっとも一般的だ。高校を卒業する前に、農場で働いたことのない人は少ない。そのため、乳製品は主食であり、ウィスコンシン州は「アメリカの酪農の地」と呼ばれるようになった。アイスクリーム、チーズ、生乳が好きな人のお腹に危ない場所かもしれない！
いつかこの辺に旅行したいのなら、知っておくべき都会はダルース市だ。スペリオル湖の西端に位置し、そこからミネソタ州の「ノースショア」と言う北岸方にもウィスコンシン州の「シェワメゴン湾」2にも車で行ける距離だ。しかし、この地方の美しさの一部は都会の喧騒から逃げられることなので、もう少し小さい町を訪れた方がいいと思う。
ウィスコンシン州の北地方についてほんの一部を紹介した。
I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer for NEAR Protocol, head of education at the Blockchain Acceleration Foundation, and a graduate student at the Tokyo Institute of Technology.
Connect with me on Twitter.
Gitche-Gumee、または&amp;ldquo;The Wreck of the Edmund Fitzgerald&amp;rdquo; - Gordon Lightfootを見てほしい。&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
ローマ字では「Chequamegon」だ。「シェクワメゴン」というスペルをみたが、現地人の発音は「シェワメゴン」だ。&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The modern dearth of intelligent crypto</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/modern-dearth-of-intelligent-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/modern-dearth-of-intelligent-crypto/</guid>
      <description>First, a quick word on recent events The original inspiration for writing on this topic was the Skyward smart contract hack for ~$3 million (at the time of the hack). However, since then, the FTX insolvency crisis occurred, so I&amp;rsquo;ve reworked and added some material to be more broadly applicable to the blockchain industry as a whole.
It&amp;rsquo;s understandable to be uncomfortable, or even scared right now. Unregulated, fast-moving markets aren&amp;rsquo;t appropriate for everyone, especially when working with money one can&amp;rsquo;t afford to lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fathomable Rust Macros</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/fathomable-rust-macros/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/fathomable-rust-macros/</guid>
      <description>Rust macros are compile-time constructs that operate on streams of Rust language tokens.
A brief aside on compilation What are &amp;ldquo;Rust language tokens&amp;rdquo;?
When a compiler begins compiling a program, it first reads in the source code file. For simplicity&amp;rsquo;s sake, let&amp;rsquo;s say the compiler stores that source code in a string. The next step is to step through the string, character by character, and divide it up into &amp;ldquo;tokens.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to speed up your code 224,444,739% using graphs</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/how-to-speed-up-your-code-using-graphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/how-to-speed-up-your-code-using-graphs/</guid>
      <description>(This article got a shout-out in Matt Parker&amp;rsquo;s follow-up video. Did you know I also make YouTube videos?)
Matt Parker of Stand Up Maths recently uploaded a video entitled &amp;ldquo;Can you find: five five-letter words with twenty-five unique letters?,&amp;rdquo; which I highly recommend you watch to understand the point of this post, the problem we&amp;rsquo;re trying to solve, and the algorithm we&amp;rsquo;ll be optimizing.
In the video, he mentions that the Python code he wrote to solve the &amp;ldquo;five five-letter words with twenty-five unique letters&amp;rdquo; problem (or the &amp;ldquo;5-5-25&amp;rdquo; problem, for short) took 2,760,670.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of Web3 in 2022</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/the-state-of-web3-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/the-state-of-web3-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of issues that web3 needs to address, and fast.
I recently attended CoinDesk Consensus 2022, and I talked to a lot of people there. The goal of this document is to answer the most common questions and address the most common themes that arose from these conversations.
Innovation transcends regulation The crypto ecosystem flails around a lot, and even as someone who works within the industry, sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to see where it&amp;rsquo;s going as a whole: the web3 world quickly transitioned from its L1 launch and ICO heyday, to the NFT craze, to the liquidity farming frenzy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage Locations in Ethereum vs. NEAR</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/storage-locations-in-ethereum-vs-near/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/storage-locations-in-ethereum-vs-near/</guid>
      <description>The keywords memory, storage, calldata are a big pain point for new Solidity developers—just look at the sheer number of questions that have been asked and articles that have been written 1 2 3 4 about the topic, not to mention the multiple, different, sections (and here, and here) the Solidity documentation dedicates to the topic.
Storage locations in Solidity are no joke!
I hope to accomplish two things in this write-up:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Compulang Podcast</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/introducing-compulang-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 14:14:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/introducing-compulang-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Check out the new Compulang podcast from GeekLaunch on Anchor and Spotify.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be covering the latest, greatest, and weirdest of tech and international news. There will also be a video version uploaded to the GeekLaunch YouTube channel with extra visuals.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to start a podcast for quite a while now, and I finally had the impetus, inspiration, and time to do it. Right now the plan is to release one episode per week, sometime over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Verify a Domain Name on GitHub with Namecheap</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/how-to-verify-domain-name-on-github-with-namecheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 17:10:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/how-to-verify-domain-name-on-github-with-namecheap/</guid>
      <description>Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be awesome to see that little &amp;ldquo;Verified&amp;rdquo; badge next to your GitHub organization&amp;rsquo;s name? (See what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about here.)
If you&amp;rsquo;re new to domain name wrangling and DNS might as well stand for Desoxyribonukleinsäure, this is a perfect place to start.
Make sure you have these things before we get started:
An organization on GitHub A domain name you&amp;rsquo;d like to associate with that organization You must have access to the DNS records for the domain name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does my RSA public key actually mean?</title>
      <link>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/what-does-my-rsa-public-key-actually-mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 23:03:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geeklaunch.io/blog/what-does-my-rsa-public-key-actually-mean/</guid>
      <description>-----BEGIN PUBLIC KEY----- MIICIjANBgkqhkiG9w0BAQEFAAOCAg8AMIICCgKCAgEApzCiydAXf4XajyD3PtiH 79vH6t2VyqbRylqW6tosNeD0rH4yyMk1HIueas2YYFlOgt2hVrnNa5zFIEKoco72 1Wu/fXlCoZzI61Zz/Q7JPJdIzeaQ+zQECsyGTZqPyADoPRoadWUqZTn7ulwMcoWb Ydg14nl+ZQLC0H6n+v3ufBFeLYB9869x7GsZkXwmrOFkVcdwzPQPObfF4CDkjICw UUKTuKWBu/WJo/NjKWDGQQL4A2RfZW6u3DLc/BHlQzHgL9Ac3hM6n/aN1IcR0UpR 4yN6KOVy2BYuGqTl91KA9dO0OlXFJkoCSeBfsME1j6DuVOlmgCtnhrdC2gOhp6Cl rEYA/DsuKMmbf2/hX//fjQ6wPKNho8izLlFMdd6ClwessTMNzemamGPQwxnUwa5K oEqCpW/LXT/Yrh/INKY9yQ7vruE/q417mJfbqfOmRitsgX4xm6IzWOb+D862Vr8y Gt931gYvRBSyh2rjLJ/EkmQHMDQN/YbtnG7MlG6jpXehWkO+3XBDiDhfVqIO3fbX k2qcJewffn3NYfeFat1WXIxSKVeIiVFPliPdDXxFTIwb5Ij+IvUrmZQbDlS/p3WT GRt6yCtdLlbGPC6YZD+WLk58/9a/EydyzIaAo5z4K9TRj3ZOIY3V2XrEJQOF3ZXn iTbKw8sfeyccOKQgWbMAo8ECAwEAAQ== -----END PUBLIC KEY----- That&amp;rsquo;s an RSA public key that I just generated using the commands:
$ openssl genrsa -out priv.pem 4096 Generating RSA private key, 4096 bit long modulus (2 primes) ..........................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................++++ ................................................++++ e is 65537 (0x010001) $ openssl rsa -in ./priv.pem -pubout -out pub.pem writing RSA key $ cat pub.pem But, what the heck is this?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
